Hello. Hello. Yeah. Who is this? Talking with Shiva Kumar. Yes. Who is this? Yeah. Hi. This is Shriya calling
on behalf of Infosys BPM. Yes. I have to tell you. Actually, your profile got screened
for the technical round and you have a telephonic round on this upcoming 14th of January. 14. Okay.
Yeah. So it will take at least I think 5 to 10 minutes. Yeah. And if you will clear that one
round, then they are going to be the virtual round. For that, the information will be shared
with you within two to three days for the virtual round. Yeah. So I am just giving you the information
that is available on this upcoming 14th of January between 10 a.m. to 5 p.m. Okay. I know the
Jabru. Inform it. Yeah. Inform it. Yeah. So you are from this testing field or developer field?
Developer. No. Because we need only developer candidates. Yeah. Okay. Okay. So only this thing,
I just have to share with you. Thank you so much. Yeah.